gridironexperts.com 2010-06-14

# Disclaimer/Privacy Policy | Gridiron Experts

gridironexperts.com cannot guarantee the correctness of information contained within, or of information obtained from third parties linked to our site.

gridironexperts.com and its resident editors, guest editors, tipsters, contributors, sponsors, advertisers, forums, email correspondence and any information appearing on this site are not meant in any way to be a source of professional advice or recommendations to in any way gamble, place bets and/or wager and no reliance is to be be placed on the same. We do not undertake any responsibility and/or liability for any losses and/or damages sustained by any person or persons using services on our site and we shall not be responsible and/or liable for any losses or damages due to any information or otherwise contained on this web site or through links, sponsors and email correspondence, whether due to inaccuracy, error, omission or bad judgment or any reason whatsoever.

Any sort of information posted on our site from other websites, persons or organizations should be checked for accuracy and timeliness at the sources themselves and no reliance should be placed on the same as it appears on our site.

We also do not accept any responsibility or liability for the comments of our viewers as may be posted on certain pages, example: message boards. If you are offended or are in any way adversely affected by such contents, please contact us immediately and refrain from visiting those pages. We are not liable to remove any offending messages on any pages within our site. Please enter at your own risk!

gridironexperts.com is not responsible in any way regarding picks and predictions posted on this site. We advised all viewers to use discretion when viewing our picks and predictions page. Please bet within your means only! If you encounter gambling problems of any kind, please contact the gambling help authorities in your area. Please visit : Gamblers Anonymous

Please check with your bookmaker for the latest odds, as odds and lines might fluctuate often without notices. We will not be liable for any incorrect odds and lines posted at our site.

Please note that Bettingadvice.com is not responsible in any way regarding placing bets through links or banners that placed on its site. All visits to our customer’s sites are purely responsibility of your own.

Although Bettingadvice.com is financed largely by funds from advertising income, we are not biased towards our paying clients in our articles and reviews. When our tipsters chose a bookmaker for their predictions, they are using the bookmaker of their choice, and Bettingadvice.com have no influence in this choice whatsoever.

gridironexperts.com does not provide gaming or gambling capabilities on its site. It is a sports information site, while odds and betting lines are part of that information. It is very important to check the laws and regulation in your own country regarding gambling betting, as it might differ from country to country.

gridironexperts.com is not responsible for any forum postings made in our forum or any sayings or claims in our chat channel. Everything said or done in these channels of cimmunications is solely the responsability of the individual who originally posted it  
Gridiron Experts Privacy Policy

Thank you for your interest in using the online information sharing service operated by Gridiron Experts . Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of the Sites. This Privacy Policy does not govern our use of any information you provide to us when you call us, write to us, or communicate with us in any manner other than through the Sites. Because the Internet is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, and held in countries (including the United States) other than the one in which you reside. By using the Sites, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 11, 2008.  
1\. Information We Automatically Collect.

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use the Sites (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Sites we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page from which you came, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit. We also use cookies (which are small amounts of data sent from a web server to your browser that are stored on your computer’s hard drive) to keep track of your use of the Sites, to validate your identity, to remember your password and preferences, to tailor the Sites to meet your personal interests, and to improve the quality of the Sites. In addition, third parties who place advertisements on the Sites may also collect information through cookies to ensure that their advertising systems and technologies work properly and to allow them to track responses to their advertisements. Cookies set by these third parties are governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. Generally, you can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you if you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to choose whether or not to accept the cookie. Please note that if you do set your browser not to accept cookies, certain areas of our Sites may not function properly.  
2\. Information You Choose To Submit.

You can visit the Sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Personal Information”). If, however, you wish to register to become a member of the Sites, you are required to provide certain Personal Information (e.g., your name and e-mail address), and we ask that you also provide a user name and password. We use your Personal Information to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve our services, and to contact you from time to time about us, our Sites, and our products and services. You may also choose to submit additional information about yourself (for example your gender, birth date, or zip code) by which someone could not personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Non-Personal Information”). Finally, you may choose to submit your alias, bio, email, photos or any other information that you would like to share with other users of the Sites (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Shared Information”).  
3\. Our Information Sharing Practices

(a) Generally. Except as otherwise described in this section of our Privacy Policy, we will never share your Usage Data, Personal Information, Non-Personal Information, or Shared Information (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “User Information”) with any third party without your permission.

(b) Advertisers. From time to time, we may share your Usage Data and Non-Personal Information to enable third parties who serve advertisements on the Sites to deliver advertisements that will be relevant to you. We will not share any such information, however, in a manner that would enable the advertiser to personally identify you.

(c) Aggregated Data. From time to time, we may share aggregated User Information with third parties. We will not share any aggregated data, however, in manner that would enable the recipient to personally identify you.

(d) Service Providers. From time to time, we may enter into relationships with third parties who provide services to us (e.g., data management and storage services or credit card processing services). In those circumstances, we disclose User Information that is necessary for such service providers to perform those services and require that they maintain the confidentiality of such User Information.

(e) Other Disclosure Scenarios. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any User Information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Sites’ infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (4) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy); and (5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity.  
4\. Public Information.

If you identify any User Information as public, you are authorizing us to share such information publicly. For example, you may elect to make certain Shared Information (such as your alias, bio, email or photos) publicly available. Also, there may be areas of the Sites (e.g., message boards, discussion rooms, and other online forums) in which you are able to post information that will be available to all other users of the Sites. By choosing to use these areas, you understand and agree that anyone may access, use, and disclose any information that you post to those areas.  
5\. Choice/Opt-Out.

We offer you the opportunity to choose not to receive communications from us. If you would like to take advantage of this opportunity, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. Please note that sometimes these requests may take up to ten business days to process and that we are not responsible for removing information about you from the database of any third party to whom we were authorized to disclose your User Information prior to processing your request. Even if you do take advantage of this opportunity, we reserve the right to send you administrative messages relating to the Sites (e.g., about changes to this Privacy Policy) and to contact you regarding any goods or services you have ordered.  
6\. Modifying and Deleting Your Personal Information.

If you would like to modify or delete from our database any User Information you previously submitted to us, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. Please note that any User Information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your request, and that if you delete certain information you may not be able to order services in the future without re-submitting such information. Also, please note that we will maintain User Information in our database whenever we are required to do so by law.  
7\. Security.

We have implemented reasonable measures to help protect your User Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your User Information, we cannot guarantee its security.  
8\. Links.

The Sites may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other website and urge you to review such practices prior to submitting any information to such websites.  
9\. Children’s Privacy.

We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Sites are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Sites to children under the age of 13.  
10\. Changes.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If under any such update we make any material change to the way in which we treat your User Information, we will inform you of such change via email or by posting a notice on relevant areas of the Sites. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date set forth therein.
